A Guide to the Equal Suffrage League Collection, 1909-1938
Library of Virginia
- Publications, Equal Suffrage League, Virginia
  - Booklets (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Broadsides (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - Broadsides (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - Broadsides (Box 7, Folder 429)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 430)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 431)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 432)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 433)
  - Programs (Box 7, Folder 434)
  - Programs (Box 7, Folder 435)
  - Programs, oversize, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 436)
  - Publications, drafts (Box 7, Folder 437)
  - Yearbooks, 1910-1916 (Box 7, Folder 438)
  - Publications, miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 439)
  - Newspaper articles, transcribed, 1913-1915 (Box 7, Folder 440)
- Publications, Equal Suffrage League, Non-Virginia
  Including Alabama, Illinois, Maryland, Massachusetts, New England, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia.
  - Booklets (Box 7, Folder 441)
  - Broadsides (Box 7, Folder 442)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 443)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 444)
  - Government Printing Office, suffrage related (Box 7, Folder 445)
  - Government Printing Office, suffrage related (Box 7, Folder 446)
- Publications, League of Women Voters
  - California pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 447)
  - Connecticut pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 448)
  - Illinois newsletter (Box 7, Folder 449)
  - Illinois newsletter (Box 7, Folder 450)
  - Louisiana broadside (Box 7, Folder 451)
  - Massachusetts newsletter (Box 7, Folder 452)
  - Minnesota newsletter (Box 7, Folder 453)
  - Minnesota pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 454)
  - Missouri pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 455)
- Publications, League of Women Voters, National
  - Achievements of ten years, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 456)
  - Booklet (Box 7, Folder 457)
  - Booklet (Box 7, Folder 458)
  - Bylaws (Box 7, Folder 459)
  - Committee on child welfare (Box 7, Folder 460)
  - Committee on child welfare (Box 7, Folder 461)
  - Committee on the legal status of women (Box 7, Folder 462)
  - Committee on child welfare (Box 7, Folder 463)
  - Committee on women in industry (Box 7, Folder 464)
  - Department of child welfare (Box 7, Folder 465)
  - Department of efficiency in government (Box 7, Folder 466)
  - Department of efficiency in government (Box 7, Folder 467)
  - Department of government and child welfare (Box 7, Folder 468)
  - Department of government and child welfare (Box 7, Folder 469)
  - Department of government and economic welfare (Box 7, Folder 470)
  - Department of government and economic welfare (Box 7, Folder 471)
  - Department of government and economic welfare (Box 7, Folder 472)
  - Department of government and education (Box 7, Folder 473)
  - Department of government and education (Box 7, Folder 474)
  - Department of government and international cooperation (Box 7, Folder 475)
  - Department of government and international cooperation (Box 7, Folder 476)
  - Department of government and international cooperation (Box 7, Folder 477)
  - Department of government and its operation (Box 7, Folder 478)
  - Department of government and its operation (Box 7, Folder 479)
  - Deparment of government and the legal status of women (Box 7, Folder 480)
  - Deparment of government and the legal status of women (Box 7, Folder 481)
  - Department of international cooperation to prevent war (Box 7, Folder 482)
  - Department of women in industry (Box 7, Folder 483)
  - Know your league, 1930-1935 (Box 7, Folder 484)
  - List of publications, 1929-1937 (Box 7, Folder 485)
  - National personnel campaign committee (Box 7, Folder 486)
  - Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 487)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 488)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 489)
  - Pamphlets (Box 7, Folder 490)
  - Pamphlets, Convention, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 491)
  - Pamphlets, Radio committee (Box 7, Folder 492)
  - Program of work, 1919-1938 (Box 7, Folder 493)
  - Programs (Box 7, Folder 494)
  - Publications catalog, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 495)
  - Special committee on immigration problems (Box 7, Folder 496)
  - New Hampshire newsletters (Box 7, Folder 497)
  - New York newsletters (Box 7, Folder 498)
  - Ohio magazine (Box 7, Folder 499)
  - Pennsylvania magazine (Box 7, Folder 500)
  - Rhode Island magazine (Box 7, Folder 501)
  - St. Louis (MO) newsletter (Box 7, Folder 502)
- Publications, League of Women Voters, Virginia
  - Broadsides (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 504)
  - Know Your League Programs 1920 (Box 8, Folder 505)
  - Newsletters (Box 8, Folder 506)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 507)
  - Programs (Box 8, Folder 508)
  - Wisconsin Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 509)
- Publications, Men's League for Women Suffrage
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 510)
- Publications, National Consumer's League
  - Pamphlet (Box 8, Folder 511)
- Publications, National Federation of Federal Employees
  - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 512)
- Publications, National Motion Picture League
  - Leaflet (Box 8, Folder 513)
- Publications, National Municipal League
  - Pamphlet (Box 8, Folder 514)
- New York City Consumers' League
  - Pamphlet (Box 8, Folder 515)
- Publications, National Woman's Party
  - Campaign Textbook, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 516)
- Publications, National Women's Trade Union League of America
  - Pamphlet (Box 8, Folder 517)
- Publications, National American Woman Suffrage Association
  - Broadsides (Box 8, Folder 518)
  - Broadsides (Box 8, Folder 519)
  - Broadsides, Foreign language (Box 8, Folder 519a)
  - Convention proceedings, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 520)
  - Convention proceedings, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 521)
  - Convention proceedings, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 522)
  - Convention proceedings, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 523)
  - Convention proceedings, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 524)
  - Convention proceedings, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 525)
  - Convention proceedings, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 526)
  - History of Woman Suffrage (Box 8, Folder 527)
  - Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 528)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 529)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 530)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 531)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 532)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 533)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 534)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 535)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 536)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 537)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 538)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 539)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 540)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 541)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 542)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 543)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 544)
  - Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 545)
  - Printed petition, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 546)
  - Printed speech, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 547)
  - Publications catalog and price list (Box 8, Folder 548)
  - Publications, mounted, with prices (Box 8, Folder 549)
  - Publications, mounted, with prices (Box 8, Folder 550)
  - Publications, mounted, with prices (Box 8, Folder 551)
  - Publications, mounted, with prices (Box 8, Folder 552)
  - Publications, mounted, with prices (Box 8, Folder 553)
  - Publications, mounted, with prices (Box 8, Folder 554)
  - Publications, samples (Box 8, Folder 555)
  - Study course, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 556)
  - Suffrage plays, catalog (Box 8, Folder 557)
  - Programs (Box 9, Folder 558)
  - Programs, Convention, 1910-1913 (Box 9, Folder 558a)
  - Programs, Convention, 1914-1915 (Box 9, Folder 559)
  - Programs, Convention, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 560)
  - Programs, Convention, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 562)
  - Report of Treasurer, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 563)
  - Yearbook, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 564)
  - Posters, Suffrage, NAWSA (Box 9, Folder 565)
  - Posters, Suffrage, England (Box 9, Folder 565a)
  - Posters, Suffrage, Virginia (Box 9, Folder 566)
  - Programs, Suffrage, England (Box 9, Folder 567)
  - Programs, Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 568)
- Publications, Progressive Party
  - Broadsides (Box 9, Folder 569)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 570)
- Publications, Suffrage, England
  - Booklets (Box 9, Folder 571)
  - Broadsides (Box 9, Folder 571a)
  - House of Commons Debate, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 572)
  - International Woman Suffrage Alliance, Report, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 573)
  - London Society for Woman's Suffrage, Annual Report, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 574)
  - National Union of Woman's Suffrage Societies, Annual Report, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 575)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 576)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 577)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 578)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 579)
  - Periodicals (Box 9, Folder 580)
- Publications, Suffrage, Miscellaneous
  - Broadsides (Box 9, Folder 581)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 582)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 583)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 584)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 585)
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 586)
  - Periodicals, fragments (Box 9, Folder 587)
- Publications, State Central Committee of Suffrage Amendment Alliance, Illinois
  - Pamphlet (Box 9, Folder 588)
- Publications, Suffrage School, Maine
  - Lessons, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 589)
- Publications, Virginia Association Opposed to Woman Suffrage
  - Broadside (Box 9, Folder 590)
  - Pamphlet (Box 9, Folder 591)
  - Anti-Suffrage lieterature, Non-Virginia (Box 9, Folder 592)
  - Virginia Suffrage News (Box 9, Folder 593)
- Publications, Wage Earner's Suffrage League
  - Pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 594)
- Publications, Women's Bureau, U.S. Department of Labor
  - Pamphlet (Box 9, Folder 595)
- Publications, Woman Citizen
  - Issue, May 1919 (Box 9, Folder 596)
  - Issue, April 1921 (Box 9, Folder 597)
  - Issue, January 1923 (Box 9, Folder 598)
  - Issue, January 1925 (Box 9, Folder 599)
  - Issue, March 1925 (Box 9, Folder 600)
  - Issue, April 1925 (Box 9, Folder 601)
  - Issue, May 1925 (Box 9, Folder 602)
  - Issue, May 1925 (Box 9, Folder 603)
  - Issue, June 1925 (Box 9, Folder 604)
  - Issue, June 1925 (Box 9, Folder 605)
  - Issue, July 1925 (Box 9, Folder 606)
  - Issue, August 1925 (Box 9, Folder 607)
  - Issue, September 1925 (Box 9, Folder 607a)
  - Issue, Fragments, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 608)
  - Issue, partial (Box 9, Folder 609)
  - Issue, Woman's Club, Chicago (Box 9, Folder 610)
- Publications, Woman's Club, Richmond
  - Fifteenth Annual Report, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 611)
- Publications, Woman's Journal and Suffrage News
  - Traveling Kampaign Kit (Box 9, Folder 612)
  - Traveling Kampaign Kit (Box 9, Folder 613)
- Publications, Woman Suffrage Party
  - Pamphlet (Box 9, Folder 614)
  - New York broadsides (Box 9, Folder 615)
  - New York pamphlets (Box 9, Folder 616)
  - New York pamphlets, Election (Box 9, Folder 617)
  - New York, The Woman Voter, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 618)
- Publications, Virginia
  - Acts of Assembly, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 619)
  - Act, Amendment of Chapter 17 of the General laws, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 620)
  - Act, providing for indigent, widowed mothers, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 621)
  - Amendments to the constitution, proposed (Box 10, Folder 622)
  - Amendments to the constitution, proposed, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 623)
  - Bill, Act to raise revenue for the support of the government and public free schools, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 624)
  - Bills, to amend and re-enact section 54 of the Code of Virginia (Box 10, Folder 625)
  - Bill, to establish minimum wage for women and minors, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 626)
  - Bill, extending the right of suffrage to women (Box 10, Folder 627)
  - Bill, granting women the right to vote for electors for President (Box 10, Folder 628)
  - Bill, to provide censorship for moving pictures, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 629)
  - Bill, to provide for the support of illegitimate children, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 630)
  - Bill, rape and seduction, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 631)
  - Bills referred, House of Delegates, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 632)
  - Code, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 633)
  - Digest of bills submitted to the General Assembly by the Children's Code Commission, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 634)
  - General Assembly, Joint Resolutions (Box 10, Folder 635)
  - Senate, Resolutions (Box 10, Folder 636)
  - House of Delegates, Resolutions, 1918-1920 (Box 10, Folder 637)
  - House of Delegates, Calendar, 1914-1920 (Box 10, Folder 638)
  - Lasw Bearing on Labor, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 639)
  - Senate, Bills (Box 10, Folder 640)
  - Senate, Calendar, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 641)
  - Congress (Box 10, Folder 642)
  - Suffrage laws, non-Virginia, 1909-1919 (Box 10, Folder 643)
  - Women's Enfranchisement Bill, England (Box 10, Folder 644)
  - Woman Suffrage, Ballot, Ireland, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 645)
- Publications, Miscellaneous
  - Broadsides (Box 10, Folder 646)
  - Chart, Health, and Recreation Bureau, Connecticut (Box 10, Folder 647)
  - Commission on Simplification and Economy of State and Local Government (Box 10, Folder 648)
  - Conference on Government Efficiency, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 649)
  - Congressional Record, 1910-1919 (Box 10, Folder 650)
  - Consitution of Virginia, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 651)
  - County Manager Form of Government (Box 10, Folder 652)
  - Daughters of the King, 1914-1916 (Box 10, Folder 653)
  - Health Department, City of Richmond, Annual Report, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 654)
  - Health Department, City of Richmond, Annual Report, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 655)
  - Hygiene and Morality (cover only) (Box 10, Folder 656)
  - Industrial Commission of Virginia, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 657)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 658)
  - Ladies' Anthenaeum Club, England (Box 10, Folder 659)
  - Map of the city of Richmond, 1912 (Box 10, Folder 660)
  - Map of the City of Richmond, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 661)
  - Non-partisan Senatorial Committee (Box 10, Folder 662)
  - Newsletters (Box 10, Folder 663)
  - Pamphlets (Box 10, Folder 664)
  - Pamphlets (Box 10, Folder 665)
  - Periodicals (Box 10, Folder 666)
  - Richmond Education Association, Annual reports, 1903-1904 (Box 10, Folder 667)
  - State Board of Public Welfare, Jackson, Mississippi, Bulletin, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 668)
  - Traveling through Historyland, pamphlet, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 669)
  - Typescript poetry (Box 10, Folder 670)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Immigration (Box 10, Folder 671)
  - Virginia 4-H Newsletter, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 672)
  - Virginia Law Register, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 673)
  - Virginia politics, 1917-1922 (Box 10, Folder 674)
  - Virginia State Highway Map, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 675)
  - World's Work, extracts (Box 10, Folder 676)
- Publications, Duplicates
  - College Equal Suffrage League (Box 11, Folder 677)
  - Consumers' League (Box 11, Folder 677a)
  - Equal Suffrage League, Virginia (Box 11, Folder 678-701)
  - Equal Suffrage League, Non-Virginia (Box 11, Folder 702)
  - League of Women Voters, National (Box 11, Folder 703-712)
  - League of Women Voters, National (Box 12, Folder 713)
  - League of Women Voters, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 714-729)
  - Men's League for Women Suffrage (Box 12, Folder 730)
  - Virginia politics (Box 12, Folder 731)
  - National Woman Suffrage Association (Box 12, Folder 732-745a)
  - Programs, Suffrage, England (Box 12, Folder 746)
  - Miscellaneous, Suffrage (Box 12, Folder 746a-747)
  - Virginia Suffrage News (Box 12, Folder 748)
  - Wage Earners' Suffrage League (Box 12, Folder 749)
  - Woman Suffrage Party (Box 12, Folder 750)
  - Amendments to the Virginia Constitution, proposed (Box 12, Folder 751)
  - General Assembly, bills (Box 12, Folder 752)
  - Senate, bills (Box 12, Folder 753)
  - General Assembly, Joint Resolutions (Box 12, Folder 754)
- Index cards (Box 13)
  Each card includes a brief history of the delegates opinion and voting record on the suffrage question recorded by a member of the Equal Suffrage League. Photographs of the delegates are attached to some of the cards.
- Scrapbooks, 1914-1919 (Box 14)
- The Woman's Journal, 1909-1912 (Box 15)
- Newspaper clippings, unarranged (Box 16)
- Newspaper clippings, unarranged (Box 17)
- Oversize newspaper clippings, unarranged (Box 18)
- Oversize newspaper clippings, loose scrapbook pages, unarranged (Box 19)
- Oversize maps and posters, 1934 (Box 20)
- Vote for Women buttons and printing plate of U.S. map (Box 21)
- Buttons, name badges, ribbons, ink stamps, glass negatives (Box 22)